Maltese, Serphin R.; Papers apap382
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Senate Subject Files, 1965-2009; 22.7 cubic ft.
  - Senator Maltese with Guests Jam Ghajar M.D., Ph.D. and Laura Iacono from the Brain Trauma Foundation, 2005 March 3 (Video-tape 38)
  - Senator Maltese with Guests Maureen O'Connor and George Stamaliades, 2005 March 17 (Video-tape 39)
  - Channel 1 Recording - Cunningham (Bloomberg Advisor) and Log Cabin Republicans, 2005 July (Video-tape 40)
  - Inside Albany, 2005 December 18 (Video-tape 41)
  - 23rd Assembly District - County Committee, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - 28th Assembly District, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - 31st Assembly District - Count Committee, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Administrative Files, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - American Legion, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Artis Drugs, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Awards, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Board of Elections - New York City, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Boyland, William, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Census Data, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Clippings (1 of 4), 2005 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Clippings (2 of 4), 2005 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Clippings (3 of 4), 2005 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Clippings (4 of 4), 2005 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Community Events, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence (1 of 2), 2005 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence (2 of 2), 2005 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Cox, Ed, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Department of Homeless Services, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Direct Mailings, Pamphlets, and Flyers, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - General Election Ballots, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Golisano, Thomas, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Hanophy, Judge Robert, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Hospital Funding, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Judges, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Juniper Berry, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Manton, Thomas - Constituent Paper, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - Megan's Law, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - New York City Landmarks, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - New York State Senate Awards, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - Newsletters, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - News Releases, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Photos, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Political Events, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Pope John Paul II, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Queens County Republican Party, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Report for Civic and Community Leaders, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Republican Press Secretary Handbook, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Republican Women's Club of Queens County, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Senate Correspondence, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Senate Memorandum, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - United Nations Reform, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Veterans, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - New York State Republican Party, 2005; 2007-2008; Undated (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - American Conservative Union, 2005-2006 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Aron-Defronzo, Susan, 2005-2006 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - C.O.M.E.T., Inc., 2005-2006 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - District Appropriations, 2005-2006 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Education, 2005-2006 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Faso, John, 2005-2006 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - immigrant Issues, 2005-2006 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Independence Party, 2005-2006 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Italian American Museum, 2005-2006 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Maple Grove Cemetery, 2005-2006 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Maspeth, 2005-2006 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - McFarland, Kathleen T., 2005-2006 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Scafidi, Andrew, 2005-2006; Undated (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Spencer, John, 2005-2006; Undated (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Atlas Park, 2005-2007 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Blogs, 2005-2007 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Calandra Italian American Institute, 2005-2007 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - St. Albans Vets Hospital, 2005-2008 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Birthday Letters, 2005-2008; Undated (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Bloomberg, Mike, 2005-2008; Undated (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Senate Majority Leader Joseph L. Bruno Speaking at the NY Conference of Mayors and Municipal Officials, 2006 February 27 (Video-tape 42)
  - Inside Albany, 2006 March 5 (Video-tape 43)
  - Capitol News Tonight, 2006 March 15 (Video-tape 44)
  - Addabbo, Joe, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Administrative Files, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Baldeo, Albert, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Ballot Count, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - Bruno/Haggerty Objectors, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - Bruno vs. Bloomberg, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - Campaign Materials, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - Christ the King Obituaries, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - Clippings (1 of 4), 2006 (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - Clippings (2 of 4), 2006 (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - Clippings (3 of 4), 2006 (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - Clippings (4 of 4), 2006 (Box 20, Folder 46)
  - Community Education Council, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 47)
  - Community Events, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 48)
  - Congratulations Letters, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 49)
  - "Constance DelVecchio Maltese - An Exhibition of Paintings", 2006 (Box 20, Folder 50)
  - Correspondence (1 of 2), 2006 (Box 20, Folder 51)
  - Correspondence (2 of 2), 2006 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - D'Amato, John, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Direct Mailings and Pamphlets, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Election Results, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Emergency Medical Technicians, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Endorsements, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Endorsements Surveys, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - General Slocum Memorial, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Glendale Organizations, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Homeland Security, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Hospital Bankruptcy and Disposition, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Italian American Legal Defense, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Italian Charities of America, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Juniper Park Civic Association, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Juniper Park Dog Park, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - LaGuardia Community College, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Legislative Resolutions, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Local 32 BJ, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Maltese Front Page - Eastern Queens Gazette, 2006 (Oversize 1, Folder 30)
  - Memorial Day Parade, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Mulhearn, Tim, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Newsletter, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - News Releases, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - New York Republican State Committee, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Photos, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Pirro, Jeanine, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Political Events, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Queens County Republican Party, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Queens Preservation, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Reich, Perry Correspondence, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Reports, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Richmond Hill Community Center, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Rosenbaum, Mary, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Scafidi, Andrew, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Schools, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Senate Correspondence, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Senate Majority, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Senate Memoranda, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - September 11th Memorial, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Star Rebate Program, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - Stuyvesant High School Alumni Association, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - Tax Credits, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - Triangle Fire Survivors Association, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - Vanderhoef, Scott, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - Veterans, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 44)
  - Weld, William, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 45)
  - Working Families Party, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 46)
  - Education Reform, 2006; Undated (Box 21, Folder 47)
  - IL Cavalience, 2006; Undated (Box 21, Folder 48)
  - Death Penalty, 2006-2007 (Box 21, Folder 49)
  - Maddis, Dolores, 2006-2007 (Box 21, Folder 50)
  - Paolucci, Anne, 2006-2007 (Box 21, Folder 51)
  - Report for Civic and Community Leaders, 2006-2007 (Box 21, Folder 52)
  - Same-Sex Marriage, 2006-2007 (Box 21, Folder 53)
  - Aqueduct, 2006-2008 (Box 21, Folder 54)
  - "Civic Virtue" Monuments, 2006-2008 (Box 21, Folder 55)
  - St. Saviour's Church, 2006-2008; Undated (Box 21, Folder 56)
  - Adams and Metzger Campaigns, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 57)
  - Addabbo Jr., Joseph, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 58)
  - Administrative Files, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 59)
  - American Conservative Union, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 60)
  - American Red Cross, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 61)
  - Baldeo, Albert, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 62)
  - Bhuiyan, Shaaker, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 63)
  - Bobbi and The Strays, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 64)
  - Clippings (1 of 2), 2007 (Box 21, Folder 65)
  - Clippings (2 of 2), 2007 (Box 21, Folder 66)
  - Community Events, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 67)
  - Congestion Pricing, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 68)
  - Correspondence, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 69)
  - Direct Mailings, Pamphlets, Posters, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 70)
  - Driver's Licenses, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 71)
  - Election - 22nd Assembly District, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Election Results and Count Book, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - "Empire State Coloring Book", 2007 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Fiumano, Arlene Memorial Service, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Franklin K. Lane High School ROTC Funding, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Gallagher, Dennis, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Hispanic Heritage Awards, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Howard Beach, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Independence Party, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Lawn Littering Legislation, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Long Island Rail Road Safety Hearing, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Maltese Bio, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Metropolitan Transit Authority, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Mitchell-Lama Housing Projects, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Nassau County Republican Committee, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Newsletters, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - News Releases, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Political Events, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Queens Chronicle Front Page, 2007 (Oversize 1, Folder 31)
  - Queens County Republican Party, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Queens Community Board 5, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Queens Flooding Relief, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Senate Administrative Files, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Senate Committee Forum on Railroad Safety, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Senate Correspondence, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Senate Memoranda, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Senate Proclamations, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Sorenson, Ronald James - Resolution, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Spitzer, Eliot, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Sunnyside Woodside Lions Club, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Triangle Fire Survivors Association, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Campaign Materials, 2007-2008 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Giuliani, Rudy Presidential Campaign, 2007-2008 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Photographs Logs, 2007-2008 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Queens Flooding, 2007-2008 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Seventh Regiment Armory Conservancy, 2007-2008 (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Veterans, 2007-2008 (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - Administrative Files, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - Affordable Housing, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - American Women in the Military, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - Buckley, William - Obituaries, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - Campaign Events, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - Chapters, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - Charter Schools, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - Citizens Union, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 44)
  - City Council Citation, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 45)
  - City Council Race - 30th District, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 46)
  - Clippings (1 of 2), 2008 (Box 22, Folder 47)
  - Clippings (2 of 2), 2008 (Box 22, Folder 48)
  - Columbus Day Foundation Gala Dinner Journal - 3rd Annual, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 49)
  - Community Events, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 50)
  - Constituents Demographics, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 51)
  - Department of the Aging, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 52)
  - Direct Mailings, Pamphlets, Posters, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 53)
  - Election Results, 15th Senate District, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 54)
  - Election Press, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 55)
  - Endorsements, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 56)
  - General Correspondence, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 57)
  - General Slocum Memorial, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 58)
  - Golisano, Tom, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 59)
  - Howard Beach - Water Contamination, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 60)
  - Hudson - Fulton - Champlain Quadricentennial Commission, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 61)
  - The Inner Circle Presents, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 62)
  - Italian Charities of America, Inc., 2008 (Box 22, Folder 63)
  - Italian Culture Center, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 64)
  - Katz, Melinda, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 65)
  - Legislation - Foreclosure Crisis, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 66)
  - Maltese, Constance - Consul General of Italy Letter, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 67)
  - Martin Luther High School, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 68)
  - Newsletters, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 69)
  - News Releases, 2008 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Powell G. - Letter, 2008 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Queens Civic Associations, 2008 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Queens County Republican Party, 2008 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Queens Elected Official, 2008 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Reports, 2008 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Resumes - Maltese Staffers, 2008 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Richmond Hill Fair CD-R, 2008 (Artifact-box 1)
  - Rudy Giuliani Presidential Committee, 2008 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Senate Correspondence, 2008 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Senate Resolution/Memoranda, 2008 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Triangle Fire Survivors Association, 2008 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Veterans, 2008 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Volkev, Dale - Senator, 2008 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Maltese 14:46 Richmond Hill, 2009 May 7 (Video-tape 45)
  - 15th Assembly District (A.D.) CD-ROM, Undated (Artifact-box 1)
  - 15th Senate District, Undated (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Administrative Files, Undated (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - American Flag, Undated (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Assisting Members and Families of America's Armed Forces, Undated (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Bumper Stickers, Undated (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Campaign Fundraising Event with Serph and Constance Maltese, Undated (Video-tape 46)
  - Campaign Poster, Undated (Oversize 1, Folder 31)
  - Christ the King, Undated (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Clippings, Undated (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Community Board 5, Undated (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Community Board 9 and 10, Undated (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Community Events, Undated (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Constituent Letters Floppy Disk, Undated (Artifact-box 1)
  - Correspondence (1 of 2), Undated (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence (2 of 2), Undated (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Daily Tribune Headline, Undated (Flat-file 3)
  - DeBragga, Joseph - Research for Plaque, Undated (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - DeFronzo, Joseph, Undated (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Del Vecchio Maltese, Constance, Undated (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Derek Paul Valentin Keith Christopher Simmonds, Undated (Video-tape 47)
  - Direct Mailers, Pamphlets and Posters (1 of 3), Undated (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Direct Mailers, Pamphlets and Posters (2 of 3), Undated (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Direct Mailers, Pamphlets and Posters (3 of 3), Undated (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Division of Crime Victim Services, Undated (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Ephemera, Undated (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Friends of Senator Maltese, Undated (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - General Contractors Association of New York, Undated (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - Glenridge Senior Center, Undated (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - Housing and Urban Development, Undated (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - Italian American Organizations, Undated (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - Jamaica Water Supply, Undated (Box 23, Folder 39)
  - Knitwear Industry Center, Undated (Box 23, Folder 40)
  - Malta Flag, Undated (Flat-file 4)
  - Maltese Biographies, Undated (Box 23, Folder 41)
  - Maltese Fundraiser Giuliani Endorsement, Undated (Artifact-box 1)
  - McAvoy, Annemarie - Biography, Undated (Box 23, Folder 42)
  - "More Police" Rally Sunnyside, Undated (Video-tape 48)
  - Newsletters, Undated (Box 23, Folder 43)
  - The Order Sons of Italy in America Grand Lodge, State of New York, Undated (Box 23, Folder 44)
  - Paolucci, Anne, Undated (Box 23, Folder 45)
  - Parisi, Guy, Undated (Box 23, Folder 46)
  - Photographs (1 of 2), Undated (Box 23, Folder 47)
  - Photographs (2 of 2), Undated (Box 23, Folder 48)
  - Photos - Wycoff Heights Hospital, Undated (Box 23, Folder 49)
  - Poll Result, Undated (Box 23, Folder 50)
  - Poll Worker Instructions, Undated (Box 23, Folder 51)
  - Queens Community District 5 District Needs Statement, Undated (Box 23, Folder 52)
  - Queens County Republican Party, Undated (Box 23, Folder 53)
  - Queens County Supports President Bush and Our Troops Pins, Undated (Artifact-box 1)
  - Queens History, Undated (Box 23, Folder 54)
  - Queens Library Adopt-A-Branch, Undated (Box 23, Folder 55)
  - Queens Schools, Undated (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Red Square Apartments and Memorial, Undated (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Re-Election Poster, Undated (Flat-file 5)
  - Reports, Undated (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Senate Administrative Files, Undated (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Senator Serphin R. Maltese Commemoration of the 97th Anniversary of the Triangle Shirtwaist Company Fire CD, Undated (Artifact-box 1)
  - Stickers, Undated (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Triangle Fire, Undated (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Unidentified Mini-DV tape, Undated (Artifact-box 1)
  - Untitled Speech by Serph Maltese, Undated (Video-tape 49)
  - Veterans, Undated (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Whitestone Republican Club, Undated (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Williams, Scott for U.S. Senate, Undated (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Winning in Politics for Property Owners, Undated (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - World Trade Center Disaster Relief, Undated (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Constituent Case Files, 1990-2008; 3.6 cubic ft.
  This series contains representative samples of constituent case files maintained by the Senator's staff from his time in office. Each folder title corresponds with the name of a constituent and most contain a Constituent Service Form that determines how the contact was initatied with the Senator's office, whether it be by phone call or mail. Each case file documents a concern from a constituent including reports of potholes, loud airplanes, hospital closures, or whether the Senator should support a bill.
  This series is arranged alphabetically by constituents' last names.
  - Allen, James J., 1997 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Barcia, Richard, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Bell, Dorothy - New York State Nurses Association, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Berryhill, Louise, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Bold, Rudolph, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Borello, Maryellen, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Bubell, Sonia, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Catholic War Veterans, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Cementina, Ednaflor, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Cencioni, Claude, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Cennamo, John, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Centrone, Marie, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Cerare, Pauline, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Cerna, Marisol, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Cernak, Anna, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Cernigliaro, Mario, 1993; 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Certo, Salvatore, Undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Certoma, Frank, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Cesario, Alice and Eugene, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Chabalik, Arlene, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Chamberlain, Ernestine, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Chamberlain, Sterling, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Chan, Evangeline, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Chaney, Barbara, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Chanlatte, Elvera, 1994; 1997 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Chau, Stella, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Chayaka, Stanley, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Chestaro, Margaret, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Chiarello, Barney, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Chiavone, Prospero, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Chichotsky, Victor, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Chicka, Susan, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Chiofolo, Vincent, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Chirichella, Dominic, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Chividian, Maria, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Christensen, Marie, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Christianson, Clara, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Christopher, Tony, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Ciano, Joseph, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Cuffari, Sharon, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - D'addario, Grace, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - D'Agostino, Anthony, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - D'Agostino, Antoinette, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Daitch, Marilyn, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - D'Alelio, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - D'Alesandro, Cathy, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Dallara, Mark, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - D'Allesandro, Philip, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Daly, John, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Damato, John, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Dambeck, Carol A., 1995 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Dambra, Constantine, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - D'Ambrosio, Angelo, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - D'Ambrosio, James, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - D'Amico, George, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - D'Amico, Patricia, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Dandrea, Vincent, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - D'Angelo, Anna, 1994-1996 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - D'Angelo, Roseanne, 1992-1994 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - D'Angelo, Sandra, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - D'Angelo, Vincent, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Daniel, Indra, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Daniles, Joseph, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - D'Anna, Ann, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Dante, Frank, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Daquaro, Linda, Undated (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Daquino, Carmela, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Darby, Joan, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Darco, Robert, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Dare, Marie, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Darmal, Arsalan, Undated (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Darow, Salli, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Dascoli, Steven, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Dato, Josephine, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Dattolico, Agnes, 1997; 2000 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - D'Auria, Joseph G, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - D'Auria, Lucy, 1996; 1997 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Davenel, Ann Marie, Undated (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - David, Janice, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - David, William I., 1994 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Davidson, Gertrude, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Davis, Christine, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Davis, Haviland, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Davis, Nancy, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Davis, Shirley, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Davria, Andrea, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - Dazzo, Josephine, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Dearing, Mark, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - DeBold, JoAnne, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - DeCapite, Maria, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - DeCesare, John, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - Deciucis, Edith, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - Dedinsky, Steve, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - Dee Li, Jia, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - Defeis, Marion, 1991-1993 (Box 1, Folder 95)
  - DeFelice, Eugene, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 96)
  - DeFrancesco, Daniel, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 97)
  - DeFronzo, Joseph, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 98)
  - Degen, Lisa, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 99)
  - DeGrange, Cecelia, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 100)
  - Deifel, Beatrice, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 101)
  - Deifik, Les, Undated (Box 1, Folder 102)
  - Del Franco, Norma, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 103)
  - Del Grosso, Linda, 1995; 2000 (Box 1, Folder 104)
  - Del Grosso, Pat, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 105)
  - Del Guidice, Chirstine, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 106)
  - Del Mastro, Rose, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 107)
  - Del Valle, Elba M., 2000 (Box 1, Folder 108)
  - Delafuente, Jose, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 109)
  - Delano, Kevin, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 110)
  - Delawrenzo, Michael, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 111)
  - Delio, Renee, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 112)
  - DeLisi, Joanne, 1993; 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 113)
  - Dell, Frank, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 114)
  - Dellutri, Jean, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 115)
  - Delmonte, Douglas, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 116)
  - DeLorenzo, John, Undated (Box 1, Folder 117)
  - DeLuca, Anthony, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 118)
  - Demiraj, Nicholas, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 119)
  - DeVoy, Doris, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 120)
  - DiCroce, Nadene, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 121)
  - Dobbs, Theodore, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 122)